<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Myles Braithwaite: weblog entries tagged in BlackBerry PlayBook.</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/tag/BlackBerry%20PlayBook/</link><description>Hoping for the Best, Imagining the Worst.</description><atom:link href="http://mylesbraithwaite.com/feeds/blog/tag/blackberry-playbook/" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 12:08:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><item><title>Thoughts on the BlackBerry PlayBook</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2011/apr/7/blackberry-playbook/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You will most likely use this when traveling and in meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has the same drawbacks as the iPad where you are really creating content on the device but consuming it. You can view/edit Excel, Word, and PowerPoint documents (though a third party application).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It looks like the fact that it doesn't include an email, calendar, contacts, and BBM is for security. But how many times are you somewhere without your phone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has a front and rear facing camera so you can do some video conferencing. Which would most likely be proprietary to the BlackBerry. Hopefully Skype will come out with something soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are going to buy it I would suggest getting some type of Cloud Storage option (like Dropbox) so you don't have to mess around with syncing files (PDF, DOC, Excel, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smaller than my iPad (could fit in your jacket pocket).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wirelessly connects to your BlackBerry for Email, Calendar, Contacts, and BBM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download books using Kobo (the Indigo book store). Amazon has a Kindle app for BlackBerry phones so they also should come out with one for the PlayBook.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has access to Documents To Go, so you can edit Excel, Word, and PowerPoint files (mostly like will cost money ~$20).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has a built in PDF reader.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It has both a front and rear facing camera. So you could do video calling off it (Skype has an application for BlackBerry phones so the might have one for the PlayBook).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The web browser is based off WebKit (which powers Apple's Safari and Google's Chrome web browsers) so it should be standard compliant (but web apps like the CRM don't work so while) (Facebook and the like work fine).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has &lt;strong&gt;Mobile&lt;/strong&gt; Flash, which isn't the full flash so I am not sure what may or may not work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It based off the QNX OS which is a variant of Unix for real-time tasks on an embedded system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The BlackBerry App Store looks okay. Most apps look more oriented towards the Enterprise user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Talk application so you can connect to Pidgin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evernote - a great note taking and searching application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I couldn't find a remote desktop client (ex when you are in a meeting you could connect to your desktop).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It has support to run Android applications but most Android applications don't run while on Android phones so if I had to guess it would be wonky support at best.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has support for an HDMI-out so you might be able to load a PowerPoint presentation on it and then display it on a projector/television (one that has HDMI support).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It has an application similar to iTunes where you could download music, movies and podcasts, but I wouldn't buy anything off it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From what I can tell from the screen shots it looks like the calendar, contacts, and email is pretty much the same design as the phone version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>me@mylesbraithwaite.com (Myles Braithwaite)</author><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 12:08:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2011/apr/7/blackberry-playbook/</guid><category>RIM</category><category>BlackBerry PlayBook</category><category>Tablet</category></item></channel></rss>