<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Myles Braithwaite: weblog entries tagged in Funny.</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/tag/Funny/</link><description>Hoping for the Best, Imagining the Worst.</description><atom:link href="http://mylesbraithwaite.com/feeds/blog/tag/funny/" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><item><title>A Spam Email Message I Got Today</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/nov/15/spam/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is some spam I received today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To&lt;/strong&gt;: me@mylesbraithwaite.com&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Subject&lt;/strong&gt;: Private Invitation&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From&lt;/strong&gt;: Mr  Yasir Ali&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;: Sat, 14 Nov 2009 09:51:01 +0100&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear: President/C.E.O.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is my pleasure to request for your honest assistance. This request may seem strange but I will crave your indulgence and pray that you view it seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Mr Yasir Ali from Pakistan. purchasing agent to leader of Jundollah militant group in Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the Pakistan Army's offensive in South Waziristan, I was mandated by a senior rebel leader to purchase arms and ammunition from a private dealer in Russia worth Ten Million American Dollars Only. The said amount was moved through Iran boarder on the 17Th of September 2009 to Russia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was quite unfortunate that upon my arrival, I immediately change my mind against purchasing of arms in the name of war of Islam. I have succeeded on diverting the fund into a security storage company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I pray to Allah to forgive me for all the innocent people killed during my service to the rebel force. I have promise my self and Allah never to involve in any form of crime to humanity through out my life time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In view of the above, I will never like to go back to Pakistan again because of my life and wish to invest this funds under your umbrella and supervision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will also seek your assistant to help me secure traveling documents for my wife and two children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In summary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I needed your assistant and protection to the funds. Base on the above detail information, I will highly appreciate if my request is given utmost priority and consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr Yasir Ali
Secure ID: **&lt;em&gt;-&lt;/em&gt;@live.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><author>me@mylesbraithwaite.com (Myles Braithwaite)</author><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/nov/15/spam/</guid><category>Funny</category><category>Spam</category><category>Email</category></item></channel></rss>