<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Myles Braithwaite: weblog entries tagged in Spam.</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/tag/Spam/</link><description>Hoping for the Best, Imagining the Worst.</description><atom:link href="http://mylesbraithwaite.com/feeds/blog/tag/spam/" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><item><title>A Spam Email Message I Got Today</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/nov/15/spam/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is some spam I received today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To&lt;/strong&gt;: me@mylesbraithwaite.com&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Subject&lt;/strong&gt;: Private Invitation&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From&lt;/strong&gt;: Mr  Yasir Ali&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;: Sat, 14 Nov 2009 09:51:01 +0100&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear: President/C.E.O.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is my pleasure to request for your honest assistance. This request may seem strange but I will crave your indulgence and pray that you view it seriously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Mr Yasir Ali from Pakistan. purchasing agent to leader of Jundollah militant group in Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the Pakistan Army's offensive in South Waziristan, I was mandated by a senior rebel leader to purchase arms and ammunition from a private dealer in Russia worth Ten Million American Dollars Only. The said amount was moved through Iran boarder on the 17Th of September 2009 to Russia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was quite unfortunate that upon my arrival, I immediately change my mind against purchasing of arms in the name of war of Islam. I have succeeded on diverting the fund into a security storage company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I pray to Allah to forgive me for all the innocent people killed during my service to the rebel force. I have promise my self and Allah never to involve in any form of crime to humanity through out my life time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In view of the above, I will never like to go back to Pakistan again because of my life and wish to invest this funds under your umbrella and supervision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will also seek your assistant to help me secure traveling documents for my wife and two children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In summary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I needed your assistant and protection to the funds. Base on the above detail information, I will highly appreciate if my request is given utmost priority and consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr Yasir Ali
Secure ID: **&lt;em&gt;-&lt;/em&gt;@live.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><author>me@mylesbraithwaite.com (Myles Braithwaite)</author><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/nov/15/spam/</guid><category>Funny</category><category>Spam</category><category>Email</category></item><item><title>Why do we need SEO?</title><link>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/jul/15/seo/</link><description>
&lt;p&gt;
	Today I received the following email:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From&lt;/strong&gt;: Petr ******* - File Extensions Resource &amp;lt;****.*******@file-extensions.xxx&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;: July 15, 2009 3:38:49 PM GMT-04:00&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;To&lt;/strong&gt;: me@mylesbraithwaite.com&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Subject&lt;/strong&gt;: Site suggestion - File extension library
	&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		Hello,&lt;br&gt;
		can you please add a link to our website File-Extensions.xxx at your page http://mylesbraithwaite.com as a useful computer file extensions resource?
	&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		Our site URL: http://xxx.xxxx-xxxxxxxxx.xxx/&lt;br&gt;
		Large file extension list and file types resource site.
	&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		Detailed site description: A huge file extension list including easy-to-understand descriptions and associated applications. Quickly search by extension, view common and most popular file extensions, and click to extension categories including audio and music files, multimedia, graphic and image file types and others.
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		I look forward to hearing from you soon.
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		Thanks a lot
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		Petr&lt;br&gt;
		File-Extensions.xxx
	&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p class="cite"&gt;&lt;a href="/photos/3723919099/" title="Site suggestion - File extension library"&gt;Screen Shot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	I took a look at the email headers and found this &lt;tt&gt;X-Mailer: LinkAssistant (http://www.link-assistant.xxx)&lt;/tt&gt;. A quick web lookup brought up an application called &lt;a href="http://www.link-assistant.com/linkassistant/" rel="nofollow"&gt;LinkAssistant&lt;/a&gt; and one of the features is:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote cite="http://www.link-assistant.com/linkassistant/"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Quickly address all partners in personalized emails.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
		Professional SEOs know how to approach owners of high-PR websites, ask them for a link and have huge chances to get it. You're even smarter with LinkAssistant. You will quickly find hundreds of &lt;strong&gt;relevant high-quality websites, instantly send out piles of personal link requests&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;convince&lt;/strong&gt; site owners to link to you.
	&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	I am not a fan of SEO but this is just crossing a line. A lot of &lt;a href="http://calacanis.com/2007/02/07/why-people-hate-seo-and-why-smo-is-bulls-t/" title="Why people hate SEO... (and why SMO is bulls$%t)"&gt;people&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/archives/000835.html" title="SEOs: the New Pornographers of the Web"&gt;more&lt;/a&gt; intelligent &lt;a href="/blog/2007/may/18/morality-and-web-marketing/" title="Morality and Web Marketing"&gt;than me&lt;/a&gt; have weigh in one this topic but I am going to reiterate one idea: &lt;strong&gt;If you write good content Google will index your site and give you a high page ranking&lt;/strong&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote cite="http://itc.conversationsnetwork.org/shows/detail4141.html"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
		90% of SEO is simple rules for building clean HTML. The other 10% is that SEOs are really just life coaches who need to transform their clients into something awesome that people actually care about. What you really need to optimize for is being awesome. And that's a bit harder than pulling some SEO out of your magic bag of tricks.
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><author>me@mylesbraithwaite.com (Myles Braithwaite)</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://mylesbraithwaite.com/blog/2009/jul/15/seo/</guid><category>SEO</category><category>Spam</category><category>Email</category></item></channel></rss>